If I can get you into the system, it will take me a
minute to throw you around and throw you around. Okay,
but
where I was, okay, that's my rule. You're
a [ __ ] idiot.
Tell me first. Hey, brother, if you did the
job, I wouldn't have talked to you.
I didn't do it. I'm not doing it for work. You're
cheating. Instead, you're doing it sitting
there. What are you doing? You're
not being paid to warm the seat. You won't get a salary. You
understand that you're just sitting there. What's the point? You
said, "Is this an office?" "Is this something?" "Were
you going to lay hands on me that day?"
As far as I know,
brother, unless you said no, you were going to lay
hands on me. You have no rights.
But yes, I can go against you.
You should maintain an official.
Maintain the rules. Brother, I don't remember. If I don't get a
booking, I don't have that. Yes,
you tell me. If I don't get a booking, I'll throw out
all the rights and rights. Right left.
I'm fine. And you keep repeating it.  I am telling you
when you are talking to whom you are talking to,
you should know a little about those who do
not listen to you. You are also an officer employee. I am also an employee. Hey, you are
not an employee. If I
can bring you into the system, it will take me a minute to throw
you away from the system and burn you. It is
okay, but where there is
no respect, how can I work? Do
n't tell me, what respect has to be earned, brother, it cannot be
equalized. You have been working hard from the beginning.
You have been taking
pocket salary for years. So I will not let
anyone take my pocket salary. It is not like that.
I will not give you a month's salary.
I will not let anyone take a fish's salary. And
I will not let you tour my entire branch for you.
Reply. I am working for you right.
But the way you have not behaved is this marriage is
very unproductive. You will drive me away. You will raise your hand and push me.
What will these things be? I have not raised my hand yet.
You should look at me once. Look at me once.
As far as I know people, people see me as a down-to-
earth person. I treat everyone well,
big and small.  I don't see that I respect the younger ones too,
if you don't ask for feedback, the question is the answer.
First of all, did you say sorry to
me? You didn't say sorry to me that day when you came to raise your
hand on me. You didn't say sorry. You didn't even say sorry. You don't
apologize. You
work in an office. So this is an office. If you don't get a job,
I didn't take action. That's why I didn't want
anyone's job. I don't want that. If a boy does
n't physically abuse me, it's okay. There was no
abuse. Brother, you didn't raise your
hand on me and come here. Nothing happened. The
two of you weren't caught together. That's wrong. It's completely okay.
I'm making it up. I'm lying.
Okay, 100%. I don't have anything now. I didn't
record the
video call. Come out. I'm not begging you because you're
working here. I'm not asking for mercy. I
came here for myself. You mean, you're
above anyone. You're not sitting on anyone's power.
I'm not sitting on anyone's. And one
thing I don't want is that no one is doing anything for me. There's a
problem with my laptop. I'm
going to Kolkata. This can be said here.  Maybe you didn't say yes, that's why I didn't
say no. Okay, it wasn't.
Where are you going tomorrow? You'll see tomorrow. There's no phone
number. I don't call the person who's been behaving badly with me since morning.
Okay, this is the first thing. If you had apologized to me
or if I had seen that I was a little bit wrong,
I would have accepted it. Okay, this is you. You're
a stupid [ __ ]. I mean, I'm
saying this. I understand. You mean, you
mean, a person has one thing: a certain
intellectual person in their head. And another thing:
you're not. I was called a stupid [ __ ]. Is
this what the office taught me? You're there. Stay
there later. Putting your head first doesn't mean working.
I'll do it anyway. I wo
n't even take rent. I've decided. Okay, I'll
tell everyone. I'll work on time. I'll leave.
And if not, okay, okay.